Finding Aid for the Mark Weber Jazz Collection, 1970-2005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photographs, Series 3.
  - Artists, Subseries 3.; 258 photographs
    - Otis, Johnny, 1921-, 1985 September 29; B&W snapshots (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Taken in downtown Los Angeles, CA.
    - Owens, Charles, 1939-, 1980 July 16; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Taken at the Bonaventure Hotel in Los Angeles, CA. Also pictured; Teddy Saunders, Doug Sides and John B. Williams.
    - Palmer, Earl, 1924-, 1983 March 20; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Taken at Local 47 in Los Angeles, Ca.
    - Parker, Evan, 1944-, 1978,1980; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Also pictured, Derek Bailey.
    - Parlato, David, 1986-2005 inclusive; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Arlen Asher, Peter Cover, Stefan Dill, Roy Durfee, Frank McCulloch, Roberto Miranda, Gretchen Parlato, Bill Ulmsted, and Mark Weber.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Anthony.
    - Paul, Les, 1915-, 2002 July 22; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Taken in NYC, NY. Also pictured; Charlie and Derek Trucks, and Susan Tedeschi.
    - Pepper, Art, 1925-1982, 1976-1982; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Taken at Donte's in North Hollywood, Ca. Also pictured; Monty Budwig, John Dentz, Mike Lang, Warne Marshe, Laurie Pepper.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Art Pepper Quartet.
    - Perrone, Father James, 1982 May 15; B&W 11x14 (Box 36)
      Taken at the Los Angeles Press Club at 600 N. Vermont Ave. Also pictured are Al Ceechi, Joanne Graver and Valda Hammick.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Katz.
    - Peters, Steve, 1986,2002; B&W snapshots (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Ken Keppeler.
    - Piazza, Rod, 1947-, 1983 December 10; B&W 8x10 and 5x7, and color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Taken in LaVerne, Ca. Also pictured, Mark Weber.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, The Mighty Flyers.
    - Pierce, Nat, 1925-1992, Circa late 1970's, 1980; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Autographed by Nat Pierce.
    - Pizzi, Ray, 1943-, 1980; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Taken at such venues as the Bonaventure Hotel, Carmelo's, $2 Bills. Also pictured; Nick Ceroli, Gary Denton, Dave Edelstein, Don Menza, Jay Migliori, Frank Strazzeri
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Don Menza Big Band and Don Menza Quintet, and Ray Pizzi Quartet.
    - Poliser, Lisa, 2001 August 25; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Pullen, Don, 1944-1995, 1984 June 16; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Queen Ida, 1978; B&W 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Taken in San Francisco, Ca. Also pictured; Al Lewis.
    - Redd, Freddie, 1928-, 1979 October 27; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Redd, Vi, 1928-, 1980 July 30; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles. Ca.
    - Redhouse, Mary, 2000; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Reichenbach, Bill, 1949-, 1979 March 16; B&W 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Reid, Rufus, 1944-, 1979,1996; B&W 8x10 and color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Also pictured; Matt Brewer, David Parlato.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Parlato, David.
    - Rhodes, Sonny, 1940-, 1978 August; B&W 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Taken in San Francisco, Ca. Also pictured, Mark Hummell and Michael Silverman
    - Richardson, Jerome, 1920-2000, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Roach, Max, 1924-, 1977 January 8; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Taken at Rumsey's Concerts-by-the-Sea in Redondo Beach, Ca. Also pictured; Cecil Bridgewater, Sulaiman Hakim, Billy Harper, and Reggie Workman.
    - Robinson, Fenton, 1935-1997, 1987 June 4; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Rodney, Red, 1927-1994, 1982 March 17; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Taken at Carmello's in North Hollywood, Ca. Also pictured, Monty Budwig, Ira Sullivan, and Ross Tompkins.
    - Rowland, Dennis, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl, Ca.
    - Royal, Ernie, 1921-1981, 1985 September 29; B&W snapshots (Box 12, Folder 30)
      Taken with the Frankie Capp/Nat Pierce big band, Juggernaut, in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, Pete Christlieb.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Capp/Pierce Juggernaut.
    - Rudd, Roswell, 1935-, 2000 March 20; B&W snapshots (Box 12, Folder 31)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, JJ Avenal and John Betsch.
    - Ruffner, Mason, 1987 June 10; Color snapshots (Box 12, Folder 32)
      Taken at Peabody's Down Under in Cleveland, OH.
    - Rush, Otis, 1934-, 1977, 1988; B&W 11x14, 8x10, and 5x7 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Also pictured, Zavan Jambagien and Tom McFarland.
    - Sams, George, 1970-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Taken in San Francisco and Upland, Ca. Also pictured; Bobby Bradford, Lewis Jordan, Larry Douglas, and Rasul Siddick.
    - Sams, George, 1978-1981; B&W 5x7 and color snapshot (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Taken in San Francisco. Also pictured; Bobby Bradford, Carleton Hoffman, Andre St. James, Lewis Jordan, Henry Peters, and Bari Scott.
    - Schwartz, Elliot, 1979 April 18; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Taken in Fullertin, Ca.
    - Scott, Tony, 2003 July 3; Color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Taken in NYC, NY.
    - Seals, Son, 1942-2004, 1987 June 26; Color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Taken in Ohio. Also pictured; Lonnie Brooks, Louis Hayes, john Powell
    - Shakey Jake, 1980; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Taken in Los Angeles. Also pictured; Hollywood Fats, Charlie Musslewhite
      See also Series 3: Series 3, Charlie Musslewhite.
    - Sharps, Jesse, 1986 March 26; Color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Also pictured; Tom Albach, Nate Morgan and Horace tapscott.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Tapscott.
    - Sharrock, Sonny, 1940-1994, 1984 June 16; Color snapshot (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sheldon, Jack, 1981 April 12; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Shew, Bobby, 1981 March; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Also pictured; Bobby Bradford, Gordon Brisker, Roy McCurdy, Bob Magnussen and Bill Mays.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Bobby Shew Sextet
    - Simpkins, Andy, 1932-1999, 1979, 1983; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Taken at such venues as the Playboy Jazz Festival at the Hollywood Bowl, Ca. Also pictured; Percy Heath, Jerome Richardson
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Cosby, Richardson; Series 3: Subseries 4, Art Pepper Quartet.
    - Smith, Courtney, 1996; Color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Jimmy, 1925-2005, 1979, 1984; B&W 8x10 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Taken at such venues as the Watts Towers Festival in Los Angeles, Ca.
      Photograph autographed by Smith.
    - Smith, Wadada Leo, 1941-, 1977 March 16; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Solder, Steve, 1980 April 19; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Also pictured, Putter Smith.
    - Stoller, Alvin, 1925-1992, 1977 September 2; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Sun Ra, 1914-1993, 1981, 1985; B&W 8x10, 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Also pictured Marshall Allen, Martin Banks, Young Chang, John Gilmore, June Tyson, and Ronald Wilson.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Sun Ra Arkestra
    - Szabo, Frank, undated; B&W 8x10 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Gerald Wilson Orchestra
    - Tabnik, Richard, 2001, 2003-2004; Color and B&W snapshots (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM and NYC. Also pictured; Connie Crothers, Sonny Dallas, Ratzo Harris, Roger Mancuso and John McCutcheon.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Connie Crothers Quartet.
    - Tapscott, Horace, 1934-1999, 1977-1981; B&W 11x14, 8x10 and 5x7 and color snapshots (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra and Sonship. Box 36 for 11x14 prints.
    - Taylor, Cecil, 1979 June; B&W 8x10 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Tedesco, Tommy, 1930-1997, 1980 may 17; B&W 8x10 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Taken at $2 Bills Club in Hollywood, Ca. Also pictured Paul Caprito, Tony Morillo and Emil Richards.
    - Tolliver, Charles, 1981 May 10; B&W 11x14 (Box 36)
    - Tompkins, Ross, 1938-, Circa late 1970's; B&W 8x10 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Taken at Donte's in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured Jake Hanna
    - Trask, Dick, 2000 August 25; Color snapshot (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Turetzky, Bertram, 1933-, 1980 February 14; B&W 8x10 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Taken at a perfromance at the Claremont Colleges in Ca. Also pictured, Mrs. Turetzky.
    - Turner, Big Joe, 1911-1985, 1980 July 30; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Taken at the first KLON Blues Festival in Long beach, Ca. Also pictured PeeWee Crayton and Mrs. Turner.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Crayton.
    - Turner, Johnny, 1977 September 9; B&W 5x7 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      Taken at the Raven and the Rose, 322 W. Sierra Madre Blvd., Sierra Madre, Ca. Also pictured Mickey Conway, Zaven Jambazian, Jimmy Thomas.
    - Ultan, Alicia, 1998-1999; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Vaughan, Jimmie, 1951-, 2004 March 31; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Putney Thomas (KUNM DJ).
    - Vignola, Frank, 1965-, 2002 July 22; B&W snapshot (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Taken in NYC.
    - Vinson, Eddie, 1976-1977; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Taken at such venues as the Rubaiyat Lounge, 1400 So. Western Ave. Los Angeles, CA. Also pictured; Bobby and Leo Blevins, George Brooks, Tommy Soul, and Barbara Wells.
      Also known as Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson.
    - Vlatkovich, Michael Pierre, 1992-2004; B&W 5x7, Color 8x12 and snapshots (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Also pictured; Bobby Bradford, Chris and Yolanda Garcia, Don Preston, William Roper.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Bradford. Series 3: Subseries 4; Bobby Bradford & The Mo'tet, Michael Vlatkovitch Trio and Quartet. See also Box 35 for color 8x12.
    - Walker, Phillip, 1977, 1981; B&W 8x10 and color 11x14 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      See also Box 35, David Ii also pictured.
    - Watts, Trevor, 2000 October 26; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Wayne, Dave, 2004 June 4; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Jimmy Bleich.
    - Weaver, Mark, 2000, 2005; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Taken at Blue Dragon Cafe and Outpost Performance Space, in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Eisentadt, Alan and Carolyn Lechusza, Paul Pulaski and Mark Weaver.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 4, Brassum, Mad Trio.
    - Weber, Mark, 1993-1994, 1999-2000,2003; Color and B&W snapshots (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Wells, Arthur, 1977 January 30; B&W 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Also pictured; Amos Delone, Michael Session and Steve Smith.
    - Wilber, Bob, 1928-, 1979 May 23; B&W 8x10 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Also pictured; John Heard and Pug Wilber.
    - Willard, Patricia, 1983 and undated; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Taken at the Hollywood Bowl, Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured; Shelly Manne and Gerald Wilson.
    - Williams, Johnny, 1980 April 10; B&W 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Member of Count Basie Orchestra.
    - Wilson Smokey, 1936-, 1978, 1980, 1982; B&W 8x10 and color 11x14 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Taken at such venues as the Pioneer Club at 88th and Vermont Ave. in Watts, Ca and the KLON Blues Fest in Long Beach, Ca. Also pictured; Charlie Brown, D.V. Chapman, Buddy Clemens, Joe Kinkaid, and Bobby Lesher.
      Also known as Mississippi Smokey Wilson. See also Box 35 for color 11x14, photograph taken by Neil Jones.
    - Wilson, Smokey, 1936-, 1978, 1984-1985; B&W 5x7 and snapshots and color snapshot. (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Taken at such venues as the Pioneer Club on 88th and Vermont in Los Angeles, CA and the San Francisco Blues Festival. Also pictured Curtis Griffen, Honey and Sonny Rhodes, Mark Weber, and Celie Wilson.
      Also known as Mississippi Smokie Wilson.
    - Wilson, Teddy, 1912-1986, 1977 March 16; B&W 8x10 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Witherspoon, Jimmy, 1923-1997, 1997 July 18 and 1979 November; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      Also pictured; Bruno Carr, Larry Gales, Red Holloway, Gildo Mahones, and Sonny Stitt.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Holloway, Red.
    - Wood, John, 1982 August 13; B&W 8x10 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Taken at Pasqualés in Malibu, Ca.
    - Wright, Lamar, 1982-1983, undated; B&W 8x10 and 5x7, color snapshots and polaroids. (Box 15, Folder 24)
      Taken at such venues as Gensel Church, Howard Rumsey's Concert by the Sea, the Parisian Room, Playboy Jazz Festival at the Hollywood Bowl, Ca. Also pictured; Willie Cook, Conte Condoli, Dexter Gordon, Benny Green, Cole Hoppin, Ali Jackson, O.C. Smith, Hank Stovall, Clark Terry, Sarah Vaughan, Gerald Wilson, and Snooky Young.
      Some photos from Wright's personal collection, including an early misdated photograph.
    - Zannes, Tim, 1995, 1997, 2000; B&W and color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 26)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured, Steve Feld, Tom Guralnick and James Moody.
      B&W photos dated 1995 Sept. 23 came with note reading "Outpost, Albuquerque, Tetragon does Coltrane. Paul Gonzales - trpt. & conducting, Tim Zannes - ts, Kanoa Kaluhina - ts, John Belzaguy - b, Kenny Battat - d, Tom Guralnick - as (sat in one tune), Steve Figueroa - p." See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Guralnick.
    - Zorn, John, 1953-, 1977 November 28; B&W 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Musical Groups, Subseries 4.; 76 photographs
    Photographs of musical groups varying in size from duos to big bands from Weber's photograph files.
    - Aces and Eights, 1987 June 4 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Cleveland, OH
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.), 1976 - 1979, inclusive; B&W 8x10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      A.E.C. performances at the Lighthouse in Hermosa Beach, Ca. and at UCLA's Schoenberg Hall, includes 8x10 photograph autographed by Lester Bowie.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Abercrombie, John; Carter, John and Series 3: Subseries 4, Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.) Box 6: Folder 8 and Box 7: Folder 1.
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.), 1976 -1979, inclusive; B&W 8x10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Artists included in photographs; John Abercrombie, Tylon Barez,Bobby Bradford, Lester Bowie, John Carter, Jack Dejonette, Eddie Gomez, Joseph Jarman, Roscoe Mitchell, David Moye, Rudolph Porter
      See also Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.) Box 6: Folder 8 and Box 7: Folder 1.
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.), 1976 June 26 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Carter, John and Series 3: Subseries 4, John Carter Ensemble, Art Ensemble of Chicago (A.E.C.) Box 6: Folder 8.
    - Art Pepper Quartet, 1982 January 16; B&W 8x10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Taken at Donte's in North Hollywood, Ca. Also pictured; John Dentz, Mike Lang and Bob Magnussen.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Pepper, Art.
    - Bill Evans Trio, 1977 May 5; B&W 8x10, some tinted blue 8x10s (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Taken at Howard Rumsey's Lighthouse, Hermosa Beach, Ca.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Gomez, Eddie
    - Black Music Infinity, 1975 May 17; Color snapshots (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Also pictured; Bobby Bradford, Stanley Crouch (bandleader), Butch Morris, David Murray and James Newton.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Bradford, Crouch, Murray and Newton.
    - Bobby Bradford & The Mo'tet Live At The Los Angeles County Museum Of Art, 2002 August 23; B&W snapshots (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Concert at the Los Angeles County Museum Of Art was recorded and published.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Bradford, Bobby.
    - Bobby Bradford Extet, 1976 September 19; B&W 8x10 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
      Taken at 34 N. Mentor in Pasadena. Also pictured; John Carter, Don or John Goldsmith, James Newton and Richard Rehwald (sans Ferris).
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Bradford, Carter, Ferris, Newton.
    - Bobby Bradford Sextet, 1976 September 5; B&W 8x10, 5x7 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
      Taken in Pasadena, Ca. Also pictured; Clovis Bordeux, Bobby Bradford, Glenn Ferris, Henry Franklin, Don or John Goldsmith, and James Newton.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Braford, Ferris, Franklin, and Newton. Series 3: Subseries 4; Bobby Bradford Extet, Bobby Bradford Mo'Tet.
    - Bobby Shew Sextet, 1981 March 15; B&W 8x10 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Taken at Gilberto's in Cucamonga, Ca. Also pictured; Gordon Brisker, Roy McCurdy, Bob Magnussen, Bill Mays and Bobby Shew.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Shew, Bobby.
    - Bonnie Janofsky - Ann Patterson Big Band, B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      18 member all-female big band.
    - Brassum, 2004 April 26; Color snapshots (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Also pictured; Dan Clucas, Harris Eisenstadt and Michael Vlatkovich.
      See also Series 3:Subseries 3 Weaver, mark.
    - Buster Cooper Sextet, 1980 August 22; B&W 8x10 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Taken at the Bonaventure Hotel in Los Angeles, ca.
    - Capp/Pierce Juggernaut, 1981 May 31; Color snapshots 3x5 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Taken at the John Anson Ford Theatre Also pictured Frank Capp, Nat Pierce, Ernie Andrews, Al Arons, Bill Berry, George Bohanon, Jeff Clayton, Bob Cooper, Buster Cooper, Bobby Efford, Alan Kaplan, Bob Maize, Ray Pohlman, Joe Roccisano, Marshall Royal, Frank Szabo, Mel Wanzo. Leonard Feather is in the background of one photo.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Royal, Ernie.
    - Charles Moffett Family, 1978 August; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Taken in San Francisco. Also pictured; Charles Jr., Charnette and Codaryl Moffett.
      Moffett, Charles, 1929-1997
    - Connie Crothers Quartet, 2001 March 26; B&W snapshots (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Connie Crothers, Ratzo Harris, Roger Mancuso and Richard Tabnik.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Crothers, Tabnik.
    - Conte Candoli Sextet, 1981 March 29; B&W 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Taken at Gilberto's in Cucamonga, Ca. Also pictured; Conte Candoli (1927-2001), Larry Covelli, Frank DeLaRosa, John Dentz, Joe Romano and Frank Strazzeri.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Covelli, Larry and DeLaRosa, Frank.
    - Dave Pike Quintet, 1981 January 11; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Autographed by Ron Escheté.
      See also Series 3, Subseries 3, Escheté, Ron.
    - David Murray Trio, 1977 January 6; B&W 8x10 and 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Taken at the Century City Playhouse in Los Angeles, Ca. Also pictured, James Newton and John Carter.
      See also series 3: subseries 3; Carter, Murray and Newton.
    - Don Menza Big Band, 1980 May 26; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Taken at Carmelo's. Also pictured; Nick Ceroli, Jay Migliori, Ray Pizzi, and Frank Strazzeri.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Menza and Pizzi.
    - Don Menza Quintet, 1981 June 14; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Menza, Don.
    - El Monte Art Ensemble, 1976 September 18; B&W 8x10 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Band members Deborah Fuss, Buell Neidlinger and Don Preston.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Neidlinger, Buell.
    - Ellery Eskelin Trio, 2000 November 6; Color snapshots (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Taken in Albuquerque. Also pictured, Jim Black and Andrea Parkins
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Eskelin, Ellery.
    - Ernie Kriuda Quartet, 1987 June 18; Color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Taken in Cleveland, Ohio. Also pictured; Joe Brigandi, Jeff Halsey and Chip Stephans.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Kriuda, Ernie.
    - Free Flight, 1983 March 30; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Jim Walker, flutes; Milcho Leviev, keyboards; Jim Lacefield, acoustic and electric basses; Ralph Humphrey, drums, percussion
    - Full Moon Ritual Band, 1978 August 18 & 19; B&W 5x7 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Taken at Pangea, San Francisco. Pictured; John Gruntfest, Henry Kuntz, Loren Means.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, John Gruntfest.
    - Gary Foster Quintet, 1980 April 19; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Also pictured; Alan Broadbent, Danny Embree, Putter Smith, and Steve Solder.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Foster, Gary.
    - Gene Russell Trio, 1980 August 23; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Taken in Los Angeles, California. Also pictured; Henry Franklin, Clarence Juhnston, and Talita. Gene Russell (b.1932- d.1981)
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Franklin, Henry
    - Gerald Wilson Orchestra, 1981 October 25; B&W 8x10 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      Taken at the John Anson Ford Theater in Los Angeles, California. Also pictured (place order and instrument played labeled on verso of photograph); Oscar Brashear, Garnett Brown, Ray Brown, Bobby Bryant, Jimmy Cleveland, Hank DeVega, Thurman Green, Roger Hogan, Paul Humphrey, Harold Land Sr., Harold Land Jr., Clay Lawrey, Shuggie Otis, Jerome Richardson, Maurice Spears, John Stephens, and Frank Szabo.
      See also names of individual orchestra members under Series 3: Subseries 3.
    - H. Ray Crawford Quartet, 1980; B&W 11x14 and Color 11x14. (Box 36)
      Taken in Pomona, Ca.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Crawford, Ray. See Box 35 for color 11x14.
    - Instant Composer's Pool, 2003 - 2004, inclusive; B&W and color snapshots (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Ab Baars, Han Bennink, Henny Davern, Toby Delius, Ernst Glerum, Tom Guralnick, Thomas Herberer, Tristan Honslinger, Michael Moore, Mary Oliver, and Walter Wierbos
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3; Davern, Guralnick,
    - Jack Sheldon Quintet, 1981 April 12; B&W 5x7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - James Black Ensemble, 1982; B&W 8x10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Taken at Alice's Keyhole Lounge in New Orleans, LA.
    - James Newton Quartet, 1976 August 7; B&W 5x7 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Also pictured, John Carter.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Carter and Newton.
    - Jasmine, 1977 March 27; B&W 5x7 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Also pictured; George Candress, Jef Feldman, Anne Golia, Vinny Golia and Ron Kornhauser.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Golia, Vinny and Series 3: Subseries 4, Vinny Golia Large Ensemble.
    - John Carter Ensemble, 1976 May 28 and October 24; B&W 8x10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Venues include The little Big Horn in Pasadena and the University of Southern California (USC)Garden Festival. Also pictured; Chris Carter, Stanley Carter, and William Jeffrey.
    - John Carter Ensemble, 1976; B&W 5x7 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Venues include; Century City, The Little Big Horn in Pasadena and the University of Southern California (USC) Garden Festival. Also pictured; Ed Brookshire, Chris Carter, Stanley Carter, James Newton Quartet, William Jeffrey and Melba Joy.
    - Kenny Davern Quartet, 2004 December 12; B&W snapshots (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Taken at the Outpost, New Mexico (recording CD). Also pictured; James Chirillo, Greg Cohen, Tony DeNicola, Matt Dobmer, and Tom Guralnick.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Davern, Kenny.
    - Kenny Davis Quartet, 1986 August 7; Color snapshots (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Taken at Club Isabella in Cleveland, Ohio. Also pictured; Bob Farrazza, Scott Kania, and Kip Reed.
    - MAD Trio, 2005 August 6; Color 5x7 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Taken at the Blue Dragon Cafe in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured are Alan Lechusza, Carolyn Lechusza and Mark Weaver.
    - Michael Vlatkovitch Quartet, 2003 May 19; B&W snapshots (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Taken in Albuquerque, NM. Also pictured; Chris Garcia - drums, Jonathan Golove - cello and David Mott - baritone. Performance was recorded and published.
      See also Series 3: Subseries 3, Vlatkovitch, Michael and Series 3: Subseries 4, Michael Vlatkovitch Trio.
    - Michael Vlatkovitch Trio, 1999 November 1; B&W snapshots (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Chris Garcia - drums and Anders Swanson - bass.